Guide to the Washington State University Irrigated Agriculture Research and Extension Center Photographs 1919-1969
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Series 1: Images created by WSU-Prosser staff, 1919-1969
  - Subseries 1: Dated images, 1919-1969
    - Bean Varieties. Bean plot, Exp. Sta. 5x7 neg. WSUP150. 1938-09-10 (Box 3, Item 38.092)
    - Leaf Chamber. Apple Orchard. 5x7 neg. 1938-09-10 (Box 3, Item 38.093)
    - Photo machines. Irrig. Orchard. 5x7 neg. 1938-09-12 (Box 3, Item 38.094)
    - P - 4 Rome Tree G. Apple Orchard. 5x7 neg. 1938-09-12 (Box 3, Item 38.095)
    - Leaf Chamber. Apple Orchard. 5x7 neg. 1938-09-12 (Box 3, Item 38.096)
    - Photosynthetic Machine. 5x7 neg. 1938-09-12 (Box 3, Item 38.097)
    - Photosynthetic Apparatus. 5x7 neg. 1938-09-12 (Box 3, Item 38.098)
    - Transpiration unit. N. Porch. 5x7 neg. 1938-09-13 (Box 3, Item 38.099)
    - Strawberry varieites. N. Porch. 5x7 neg.; print. 1938-09-13 (Box 3, Item 38.100)
    - Transpiration unit. N. Porch. 5x7 neg.; print. 1938-09-13 (Box 3, Item 38.101)
    - Unfertilized alfalfa plot. Johansen's. 5x7 neg.; print. 1938-06-01 (Box 3, Item 38.102)
    - Phosphorus plot 120# per acre applied April 10, 1938. Alfalfa seeded 1937. Phosphate at rate of about 700# treble. Johansen's. 5x7 neg.; 2 prints. 1938-06-01 (Box 3, Item 38.103)
    - Beets on Plot 2. Outlook plots. 3 persons - Clore?. 5x7 neg.; 2 prints. WSUP109. 1938-07-14 (Box 3, Item 38.104a)
    - Beets on Plot 2. Outlook plots. 3 persons - Clore?;. 5x7 neg. 1938-07-14 (Box 3, Item 38.104b)
    - Corn crossing plot. S.of corn. 5x7 neg.; print. 1938-09-08 (Box 3, Item 38.106)
    - Corn crossing plot. S.of corn. 5x7 neg.; print. 1938-09-08 (Box 3, Item 38.107)
    - Corn crossing plot. S.of corn. 5x7 neg.; print. 1938-09-08 (Box 3, Item 38.108)
    - Corn crossing plot. S.of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1938-09-08 (Box 3, Item 38.109)
    - Corn crossing plot. S.of corn. 5x7 neg.; print. 1938-09-08 (Box 3, Item 38.110)
    - Plot 6 - Alf. Fert. Exp. South of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1938-09-17 (Box 3, Item 38.111)
    - Plot 7 - Alf. Fert. Plots. South of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1938-09-17 (Box 3, Item 38.112)
    - Plot 9 - Alf. Fert. Exp. South of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1938-09-17 (Box 3, Item 38.113)
    - Plot 10 - Alf. Fert. Exp. South of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1938-09-17 (Box 3, Item 38.114)
    - Plot 11 - Alf. Fert. Exp. South of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1938-09-17 (Box 3, Item 38.115)
    - Plot 12 - Alf. Fert. Exp. South of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1938-09-17 (Box 3, Item 38.116)
    - Plot 21 - Alf. Fert. Exp. South of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1938-09-17 (Box 3, Item 38.117)
    - Plot 23 - Alf. Fert. Exp. South of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1938-09-17 (Box 3, Item 38.118)
    - South Dakota 12. Alfalfa, 3rd cutting (1933). E.of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1938-09-17 (Box 3, Item 38.119)
    - Turkestan alfalfa 3rd cutting, 1933 seeding. E.of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1938-09-17 (Box 3, Item 38.120)
    - Hardistan alfalfa (1933) 3rd cutting. E.of plot. 5x7 neg.; 2 prints. 1938-09-17 (Box 3, Item 38.121)
    - Ladak - 3rd cutting. 1933 seeding. E.of plot. 5x7 neg.; 2 prints. 1938-09-17 (Box 3, Item 38.122)
    - Grimm (N.D.) 3rd cutting. 1933 seeding. E.of plot. 5x7 neg.; 4 prints. 1938-09-17 (Box 3, Item 38.123)
    - Lima beans. N. Porch. 5x7 neg.; print. 1938-09-21 (Box 3, Item 38.124)
    - Lima beans. N. Porch. 5x7 neg.; print. 1938-09-21 (Box 3, Item 38.125)
    - Alfalfa plant Plot No. 22. S of plant. 5x7 neg.; print. 1938-09-23 (Box 3, Item 38.126)
    - Alfalfa plant Plot No. 25. S of plant. 5x7 neg. 1938-09-23 (Box 3, Item 38.127)
    - Plot 3. Wilt and mosaic alfalfa plants. S of plant. 5x7 neg. 1938-09-23 (Box 3, Item 38.128)
    - Alfalfa plant.Plot 1. Designated as No. 1. Use for above ground symptoms of witches' broom. S of plant. 5x7 neg. 1938-09-23 (Box 3, Item 38.129)
    - Tomato varieties. N. Porch. 5x7 neg. 1938-09-26 (Box 3, Item 38.130)
    - Tomato varieties. N. Porch. 5x7 neg. 1938-09-26 (Box 3, Item 38.131)
    - Cork spot. N. Porch. 5x7 neg.; print. 1938-09-26 (Box 3, Item 38.132)
    - Cork spot. N. Porch. 5x7 neg. 1938-09-26 (Box 3, Item 38.133)
    - Tomato varieties. Clark's Early - Pearson C65 should be Stokesdale. N. Porch. 5x7 neg. 1938-09-26 (Box 3, Item 38.134)
    - Tomato varieties. N. Porch. 5x7 neg. 1938-09-26 (Box 3, Item 38.135)
    - Lima beans. N. Porch. 5x7 neg. 1938-09-30 (Box 3, Item 38.136)
    - Peaches - Hale. N. Porch. 5x7 neg. 1938-09-30 (Box 3, Item 38.137)
    - Lima beans. Warren - near Benton City. 5x7 neg. 1938-10-07 (Box 3, Item 38.138)
    - Lima beans. 5x7 neg. 1938 (Box 3, Item 38.139)
    - Rockhill Strawberries. B2 I.B.E.S. 5x7 neg.; print. 1938-10-08 (Box 3, Item 38.140)
    - Tobacco plant. 5x7 neg. 1938-10-08 (Box 3, Item 38.141)
    - Boysenberry and Nectarberries. BS I.B.E.S. 5x7 neg. 1938-10-08 (Box 3, Item 38.142)
    - Lima beans. N. Porch. 5x7 neg. 1938-10-08 (Box 3, Item 38.143)
    - Raspberry - Indian Summer. B2 - I.B.C.S. 5x7 neg. 1938-10-08 (Box 3, Item 38.144)
    - President Plum. Same as 1. 5x7 neg. 1938-10-13 (Box 3, Item 38.145)
    - President Plum. 5x7 neg. 1938-10-13 (Box 3, Item 38.146)
    - Apple Tree - P2T, Orchard Irrigation. 5x7 neg. WSUP110. 1938-10-15 (Box 3, Item 38.147)
    - 1st year asparagus. NE corner asparagus. 5x7 neg.; print. 1938-10-27 (Box 3, Item 38.148)
    - Asparagus plant disease. A4. 5x7 neg.; print. 1938-10-27 (Box 3, Item 38.149)
    - Alfalfa plant -- left, normal; right, wilt. N. Porch. 5x7 neg. 1938-10-18 (Box 3, Item 38.150)
    - Alfalfa leaves: Upper - wilt, Lower - normal. 5x7 neg. 1938-10-18 (Box 3, Item 38.151)
    - Alfalfa leaves: Upper - wilt, Lower - normal. N. Porch. 5x7 neg. 1938-10-18 (Box 3, Item 38.152)
    - Alfalfa leaves: Upper - wilt, Lower - normal. N. Porch. 5x7 neg. 1938-10-18 (Box 3, Item 38.153)
    - Alfalfa plant -- left, normal; right, wilt. Under-explosed. N. Porch. 5x7 neg. 1938-10-18 (Box 3, Item 38.154)
    - Russian Knapweed. Lewis Place - Toppenish. 3 people - Schafer, Narvey, Seely. 5x7 neg. WSUP151. 1938-10-21 (Box 3, Item 38.155)
    - Russian Knapweed. Lewis Place - Toppenish. 3 people - Schafer, Narvey, Seely. 5x7 neg. 1938-10-21 (Box 3, Item 38.156)
    - Russian Knapweed. Lewis Place - Toppenish. 5x7 neg. 1938-10-21 (Box 3, Item 38.157)
    - Alkali check plots. Outlook plots. 5x7 neg. 1938-11-03 (Box 3, Item 38.158)
    - Alkali check plots. Outlook plots. 5x7 neg. 1938-11-03 (Box 3, Item 38.159)
    - Alkali check plots. Outlook plots. 5x7 neg. 1938-11-03 (Box 3, Item 38.160)
    - Alkali check plots. Outlook plots. 5x7 neg. 1938-11-03 (Box 3, Item 38.161)
    - Sugar beets. Outlook plots. 5x7 neg. 1938-11-03 (Box 3, Item 38.162)
    - Sugar beets. Outlook plots. 5x7 neg. 1938-11-03 (Box 3, Item 38.163)
    - Sugar beets. Outlook plots. 5x7 neg. 1938-11-03 (Box 3, Item 38.164)
    - Sugar beets. N. Porch Outlook Plots. 5x7 neg. 1938-11-04 (Box 3, Item 38.165)
    - Sugar beets. N. Porch Outlook Plots. 5x7 neg. 1938-11-04 (Box 3, Item 38.166)
    - Sugar beets. N. Porch Outlook Plots. 5x7 neg. 1938-11-04 (Box 3, Item 38.167)
    - Sugar beets. N. Porch Outlook Plots. 5x7 neg. 1938-11-04 (Box 3, Item 38.168)
    - Diagram plot arrangement. 5x7 neg. 1938 (Box 3, Item 38.169)
    - Cultural irrigation and yield data. 5x7 neg. 1938 (Box 3, Item 38.170)
    - Irrigation of Outlook Plots (Taken from photograph). 5x7 neg. 1938 (Box 3, Item 38.171)
    - Growth of barley, Outlook Plots 1937 (Taken from photograph). 5x7 neg. 1938 (Box 3, Item 38.172)
    - Beets on Outlook Plots 1937 (Taken from photograph). 5x7 neg. 1938 (Box 3, Item 38.173)
    - Outlook Plots (Taken from photograph). 5x7 neg. 1938 (Box 3, Item 38.174)
    - Outlook Plots (Taken from photograph). 5x7 neg. 1938 (Box 3, Item 38.175)
    - Summary Table of Alfalfa varieties. 5x7 neg. 1938 (Box 3, Item 38.176)
    - Graph of 1934 - 38 yields inclusive, Ariz. Common, So Dakota 12, and Grimm. 5x7 neg. 1938 (Box 3, Item 38.177)
    - Graph of 1934 - 38 yields inclusive, So Dakota 12, Ladak, Turkestan and Hardistan. 5x7 neg. 1938 (Box 3, Item 38.178)
    - Summary of yield deviations in alfalfa fert. experiment 1932 - 1938, inclusive. 5x7 neg. 1938 (Box 3, Item 38.179)
    - Pedigree of Iowa 939. 5x7 neg. 1938 (Box 3, Item 38.180)
    - Pedigree of Iowa 939. 5x7 neg.; print. 1938 (Box 3, Item 38.181)
    - Diagram showing crossing of inbreds and single crosses to produce double cross. 5x7 neg. 1938 (Box 3, Item 38.182)
    - Crib of corn - 1938. 5x7 neg. 1938 (Box 3, Item 38.184)
    - Ins. Br. Exp. Station Field Day Negatives by Eddy (1938). 12 negatives of varying sizes. Columbia Basin Project. WSUP111-WSUP123. 1938-08-02 (Box 3, Item 38.185)
    - Fertilizer Plots, Benton City (Wm. Muldrow). Left - check plot; Right - fertilized 700# Treble. Hand-Johansens. 2 3x4 negs. 1938-06-01 (Box 3, Item 38.186)
    - Fertilizer movement under irrigation. 5x7 neg. 1938 (Box 3, Item 38.187)
    - Plot 2 - Outlook plots. Description? See also 38.41. 5x7 neg. 1938-07-14 (Box 3, Item 38.188)
    - Field Day. South Building. 3x4 neg. WSUP125. 1939 (Box 3, Item 39.001a)
    - Listing for Ridge Planting of Beets. Sugar Beets. 5x7 neg. WSUP124. 1939-03-22 (Box 3, Item 39.001b)
    - Listing for ridge planting of beets. Field C3. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-03-22 (Box 3, Item 39.002)
    - Niffon prune grape. Same vine as 39 - 4. E of vine. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-03-24 (Box 3, Item 39.003)
    - Grape vine marked for purning by Niffon system. E of vine. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-03-24 (Box 3, Item 39.004)
    - Wheat on Plot 1. Nitrogen fertilizer experiment. N. of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-07-17 (Box 3, Item 39.005)
    - Wheat on Plot 2. Nitrogen fertilizer experiment. N. of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-07-17 (Box 3, Item 39.006)
    - Wheat on Plot 3. Nitrogen fertilizer experiment. N. of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-07-17 (Box 3, Item 39.007)
    - Wheat on Plot 4. Nitrogen fertilizer experiment. N. of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-07-17 (Box 3, Item 39.008)
    - Wheat on Plot 5. Nitrogen fertilizer experiment. N. of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-07-19 (Box 3, Item 39.009)
    - Wheat on Plot 6. Nitrogen fertilizer experiment. N. of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-07-19 (Box 3, Item 39.010)
    - Wheat on Plot 7. Nitrogen fertilizer experiment. N. of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-07-19 (Box 3, Item 39.011)
    - Wheat on Plot 9. Nitrogen fertilizer experiment. N. of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-07-19 (Box 3, Item 39.012)
    - Wheat on Plot 10. Nitrogen fertilizer experiment. N. of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-07-19 (Box 3, Item 39.013)
    - Wheat on Plot 11. Nitrogen fertilizer experiment. N. of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-07-19 (Box 3, Item 39.014)
    - Wheat on Plot 12. Nitrogen fertilizer experiment. N. of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-07-19 (Box 3, Item 39.015)
    - Wheat on Plot 13. Nitrogen fertilizer experiment. N. of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-07-19 (Box 3, Item 39.016)
    - Wheat on Plot 14. Nitrogen fertilizer experiment. N. of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-07-19 (Box 3, Item 39.017)
    - Wheat on Plot 15. Nitrogen fertilizer experiment. N. of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-07-19 (Box 3, Item 39.018)
    - Four Field Day pictures. See also 39.00. 3.25x4.25 neg.; 3 prints. WSUP154. 1939-07-27 (Box 3, Item 39.019)
    - Fertilizer plots - Walla Walla plots. S. of plots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-08-02 (Box 3, Item 39.020)
    - Fertilizer plots - Walla Walla plots. S. of plots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-08-02 (Box 3, Item 39.021)
    - Fertilizer plots - Walla Walla plots. S. of plots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-08-02 (Box 3, Item 39.022)
    - Fertilizer plots - Walla Walla plots. S. of plots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-08-02 (Box 3, Item 39.023)
    - Fertilizer plots - Walla Walla plots. S. of plots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-08-02 (Box 3, Item 39.024)
    - Fertilizer plots - Walla Walla plots - P 11A. S. of plots. 5x7 neg.; print. WSUP152. 1939-08-02 (Box 3, Item 39.025)
    - Fertilizer plots - Walla Walla plots - P 21. S. of plots. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-08-02 (Box 3, Item 39.026)
    - Fertilizer plots - Walla Walla plots - P 20. 5x7 neg.; print. WSUP153. 1939-08-02 (Box 3, Item 39.027)
    - Fertilizer plots - Walla Walla plots - P 19. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-08-02 (Box 3, Item 39.028)
    - Fertilizer plots - Walla Walla plots - P 18. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-08-02 (Box 3, Item 39.029)
    - Irrigation of sugar beets showing type of distribution. 5x7 neg. 1939-08-07 (Box 3, Item 39.030)
    - Planting of sugar beets. 75% moisture plot. N. of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-08-07 (Box 3, Item 39.032)
    - Irrigation of potatoes - Every furrow 80% moisture plot. N. of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-08-07 (Box 3, Item 39.033)
    - Riege planting - Sugar beets. 75% moisture plot. N. of plot. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-08-07 (Box 3, Item 39.034)
    - Tomato curly top. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-08-08 (Box 3, Item 39.035)
    - Grape varieties. N. porch. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-08-08 (Box 3, Item 39.036)
    - Diagram - tree fruit variety planting. N. porch. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-08-08 (Box 3, Item 39.037)
    - Lima bean varieties. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-08-23 (Box 3, Item 39.038)
    - Grapes on American Fruit Grower ranch near Qunicy. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-09-02 (Box 3, Item 39.039)
    - Sprinkler Irrigation of Lima Beans. Am. Fruit Growers. Near Quincy. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-09-02 (Box 3, Item 39.040)
    - Pedigree of Iowa 939 - Hybrid corn. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939 (Box 3, Item 39.041)
    - Lima bean field - American Fruit Growers near Quincy. Near Quincy. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-09-02 (Box 3, Item 39.042)
    - Location map of Irrigation Branch Experiment Station. 3.25x4.25 neg.; print. 1939 (Box 3, Item 39.043)
    - Location map of Irrigation Branch Experiment Station. 5x7 neg.; print. WSUP155. 1939 (Box 3, Item 39.044)
    - Vineyard of Franz Riesling. Upland Winery. 5x7 neg. 1939-09-22 (Box 3, Item 39.045)
    - Zinfandel Grapes. Upland Winery. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-09-22 (Box 3, Item 39.046)
    - President plum. Plum Orchard. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-09-26 (Box 3, Item 39.047)
    - President plum. Plum Orchard. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-09-26 (Box 3, Item 39.048)
    - Raking with side delivery rake. C2. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-09-29 (Box 3, Item 39.049)
    - Raking with side delivery rake. Alfalfa. 5x7 neg. WSUP126. 1939-09-29 (Box 3, Item 39.050)
    - Raking with side delivery rake. C2. 5x7 neg. 1939-09-29 (Box 3, Item 39.051)
    - Raking with side delivery rake. C2. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-09-29 (Box 3, Item 39.052)
    - Raking with side delivery rake. C2. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-09-29 (Box 3, Item 39.053)
    - Raking with side delivery rake. C2. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-09-29 (Box 3, Item 39.054)
    - Raking with side delivery rake. C2. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-09-29 (Box 3, Item 39.055)
    - Viner for lima beans. Benton City (Johansen's). 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-10-05 (Box 3, Item 39.056)
    - Viner for lima beans. Benton City (Johansen's). 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-10-05 (Box 3, Item 39.057)
    - Lima beans planted July 10-12. Benton City (Jacobsen). 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-10-05 (Box 3, Item 39.058)
    - Lima beans. Benton City (Jacobsen). 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-10-05 (Box 3, Item 39.059)
    - Location map of Irrigation Branch Experiment Station. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-10-06 (Box 3, Item 39.060)
    - Location map of Irrigation Branch Experiment Station. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-10-06 (Box 3, Item 39.061)
    - Asparagus field adjoing sage brush. Lloyd Miller's, Sunnyside. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-10-06 (Box 3, Item 39.062)
    - Lim beans from single plant. N. porch. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-10-06 (Box 3, Item 39.063)
    - Lima beans from single plant. N. porch. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-10-06 (Box 3, Item 39.064)
    - Walla Walla Field Day. 3.25x4.25 neg.; print. 1939-08-02 (Box 3, Item 39.065)
    - Vining Lima beans. Johansens. 5x7 neg.; print. WSUP156. 1939-10-11 (Box 3, Item 39.066)
    - Chlorosis of Jonathan apples. N. porch. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-10-12 (Box 3, Item 39.067)
    - Diseased cherry leaves. N. porch. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-10-12 (Box 3, Item 39.068)
    - Rockhill Strawberries. N. porch. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-10-12 (Box 3, Item 39.069)
    - Lima beans from single plant - Jacobson. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-10-28 (Box 3, Item 39.070)
    - Lima beans from single plant - Jacobson. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-10-28 (Box 3, Item 39.071)
    - Lima beans from single plant - Jacobson. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-10-28 (Box 3, Item 39.072)
    - Utah, Common and Ladak. E-1. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-11-11 (Box 3, Item 39.073)
    - Utah, Common and Ladak. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-11-16 (Box 3, Item 39.074)
    - Arizona, Common and Hardistan. E-1. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-11-16 (Box 3, Item 39.075)
    - Arizona, Common and Hardistan. E-1. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-11-16 (Box 3, Item 39.076)
    - Alfalfa Variety Plots. E-1. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-11-16 (Box 3, Item 39.077)
    - Peruvian alfalfa plant. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-11-16 (Box 3, Item 39.078)
    - Turkestan alfalfa. A-5. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-11-16 (Box 3, Item 39.079)
    - Alfalfa Varieties. E-1. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939-11-16 (Box 3, Item 39.080)
    - Diagram of Miller plots - Sunnyside. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939 (Box 3, Item 39.081)
    - Diagram showing winter minimum temperatures and alfalfa yields. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939 (Box 3, Item 39.082)
    - Plot arrangement - Alfalfa Fertilizer Experiment. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939 (Box 3, Item 39.083)
    - Map of Irrigation Branch Experiment Station. Print. 1939 (Box 3, Item 39.084)
    - Aerial Maps - Irrigation Branch Experiment Station. 3.25x4.25 neg.; 2 prints. WSUP157. 1939 (Box 3, Item 39.085)
    - Diagrom of Miller plots - Sunnyside. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939 (Box 3, Item 39.086)
    - Location maps of Station in relation to irrigated areas. 5x7 neg. 1939 (Box 3, Item 39.087)
    - Copy of Map of Township 9-25. Roza Project. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939 (Box 3, Item 39.089)
    - Economics of Sunnyside Irrigation District. Benton City. Total crops for 11 years. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939 (Box 3, Item 39.090)
    - Economics of Sunnyside Irrigation District. Early potatoes. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939 (Box 3, Item 39.092)
    - Economics of Sunnyside Irrigation District. Apples. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939 (Box 3, Item 39.093)
    - Economics of Sunnyside Irrigation District. Miscellaneous crops. 5x7 neg.; print. 1939 (Box 3, Item 39.094)
    - Experimental sheep. E3. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940-03-08 (Box 3, Item 40.001)
    - Experimental sheep. E3. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940-03-08 (Box 3, Item 40.002)
    - Experimental sheep. E3. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940-03-08 (Box 3, Item 40.003)
    - Experimental lambs. Shearing Camp. 5x7 neg. 1940-04-08 (Box 3, Item 40.004)
    - Experimental lambs. Shearing camp. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940-04-08 (Box 3, Item 40.005)
    - Japanese lilac. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940-05-01 (Box 3, Item 40.006)
    - Walla Walla Fertilizer Plot 3 (Manure 16 tons). Walla Walla. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940-07-22 (Box 3, Item 40.007)
    - Walla Walla Fertilizer Plot 2 (no treatment). Walla Walla. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940-07-22 (Box 3, Item 40.008)
    - Walla Walla Fertilizer Plot 23 (Straw 2 tons + 160-80-0). Walla Walla. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940-07-22 (Box 3, Item 40.009)
    - Walla Walla Fertilizer Plot 13 (80-80-0). Walla Walla. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940-07-22 (Box 3, Item 40.010)
    - Walla Walla Fertilizer Plot 4 (Manure- 8 tons). Walla Walla. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940-07-22 (Box 3, Item 40.011)
    - Diseased sweet corn leaf. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940-07-25 (Box 3, Item 40.012)
    - Diseased sweet corn leaf. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940-07-25 (Box 3, Item 40.013)
    - Hay cutting and weighing crew. E4. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940-09-18 (Box 3, Item 40.014)
    - Hay cutting and weighing crew. E4. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940-09-18 (Box 3, Item 40.015)
    - Alfalfa fertilizers. Plot 21. E4. 5x7 neg.; print. WSUP158. 1940-09-18 (Box 3, Item 40.016)
    - Alfalfa fertilizers. Plot 20. E4. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940-09-18 (Box 3, Item 40.017)
    - Feed manger. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940-10-09 (Box 3, Item 40.018)
    - Hay conveyor. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940-10-09 (Box 3, Item 40.019)
    - Delicious starch test (a better one). 5x7 neg.; print. 1940-11-05 (Box 3, Item 40.020)
    - Delicious starch test (best). Office. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940-11-05 (Box 3, Item 40.021)
    - Delicious starch test. Office. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940-11-05 (Box 3, Item 40.022)
    - Delicious starch test. Office. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940-11-05 (Box 3, Item 40.023)
    - Rome Beauty starch test. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940-11-06 (Box 3, Item 40.024)
    - Apple starch standard (a better one). Office. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940-11-07 (Box 3, Item 40.025)
    - Winesap starch test. Office. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940-11-07 (Box 3, Item 40.026)
    - Winesap starch test. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940-11-07 (Box 3, Item 40.027)
    - Apple starch standard (a better one). Office. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940-11-07 (Box 3, Item 40.028)
    - Apple starch standard (best). Office. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940-11-07 (Box 3, Item 40.029)
    - Sweet corn. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940 (Box 3, Item 40.030)
    - Strawberries. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940 (Box 3, Item 40.031)
    - Soils map - Roza Project, Part 2. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940 (Box 3, Item 40.032)
    - Soils map - Roza Project, Part 3. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940 (Box 3, Item 40.033)
    - Soils map - Roza Project, Part 1. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940 (Box 3, Item 40.034)
    - Minimum temperatures and alfalfa yields. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940 (Box 3, Item 40.035)
    - Copy of Aerial map of the Station. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940 (Box 3, Item 40.036)
    - Copy of Aerial map of the Station. 5x7 neg. 1940 (Box 3, Item 40.037)
    - Plum sunscald. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940 (Box 3, Item 40.038)
    - Strawberries. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940 (Box 3, Item 40.039)
    - Sweet corn. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940 (Box 3, Item 40.040)
    - Starch Studies - Plots 2-I to 8-K. Basement. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940-12-07 (Box 3, Item 40.041)
    - Starch Studies - Plots 2-I to 8-K. Basement. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940-12-07 (Box 3, Item 40.042)
    - Starch Studies. Plots 10-C, 10-I and 16-I. Basement. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940-12-07 (Box 3, Item 40.043)
    - Starch studies.Plots 16-J to 20-L. Basement. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940-12-07 (Box 3, Item 40.044)
    - Starch studies. Plots 2-B to 10-D. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940-12-07 (Box 3, Item 40.045)
    - Starch studies. Rome variety. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940-12-07 (Box 3, Item 40.046)
    - Starch studies. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940-12-07 (Box 3, Item 40.047)
    - Starch studies.8-P - 2-B to 10-D. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940-12-07 (Box 3, Item 40.048)
    - Starch studies.14-F to 20-H. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940-12-07 (Box 3, Item 40.049)
    - Starch studies.10-P -3 to 14-E. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940-12-07 (Box 3, Item 40.050)
    - Starch studies.11 - 14-F to 20-H. 5x7 neg.; print. 1940-12-07 (Box 3, Item 40.051)
    - Location map of Irrigation Branch Experiment Station. 3.25x4.25 neg. 1940 (Box 3, Item 40.052)
    - Potato fertilizers. D1. 5x7 neg.; print. 1941-06-02 (Box 4, Item 41.001)
    - Tomatoes. 1st row - Treated right; 2nd row - All treated; 3rd row - Treated left. B2. 5x7 neg.; print. 1941-06-02 (Box 4, Item 41.002)
    - Tomatoes. 1st row - Treated right; 2nd row - All treated; 3rd row - Treated left. B2. 5x7 neg.; print. 1941-06-02 (Box 4, Item 41.003)
    - Tomatoes. 1st row - Treated right; 2nd row - All treated; 3rd row - Treated left. B2. 5x7 neg. 1941-06-02 (Box 4, Item 41.004)
    - Thinning studies - Plums. 5x7 neg.; print. 1941-07-18 (Box 4, Item 41.005)
    - Flume. West of flume. 5x7 neg.; print. 1941-07-19 (Box 4, Item 41.006)
    - Flume on C3. East of flume. 5x7 neg. 1941-07-19 (Box 4, Item 41.007)
    - Second cutting - Ladak. East of B5. 5x7 neg. 1941-08-02 (Box 4, Item 41.008)
    - Second cutting - Ladak. East of B5. 5x7 neg.; print. 1941-08-02 (Box 4, Item 41.009)
    - Fall, 1941. Pumpkin field. 5x7 neg.; print. 1941 (Box 4, Item 41.010)